{
    "question": "Jelaskan dan berikan contoh verb,noun,adjective,and adverbs",
    "attachments": [],
    "answers": [
        {
            "answer": "<span><span>\"Joe ate his\u00a0banana.\"</span>\u00a0-\u00a0noun</span><span><span>\"They\u00a0ran\u00a0all the way home.\"</span>\u00a0-\u00a0verb</span><span><span>\"You are a\u00a0pretty\u00a0girl.\"</span>\u00a0-\u00a0adjective</span><span><span>\"He\u00a0quietly\u00a0opened the door.\"</span>\u00a0-\u00a0<span>adverb</span></span>",
            "attachments": []
        },
        {
            "answer": "verb : kata kerja contoh : sitdown,stand up,laughing<br>noun : kata benda conntoh : chair,pencilcase<br>adverb : kata keterangan contoh : now,yesterday,tomorrow<br>",
            "attachments": []
        }
    ],
    "related_questions": [
        {
            "slug": "buatlah-naskah-drama-komedi-b-inggris-dengan-pemeran-5-atau-6-or-399",
            "question": "Buatlah naskah drama komedi b. inggris dengan pemeran 5 atau 6 orang!",
            "attachments": [],
            "answers": [
                {
                    "answer": "<span><span>Naughty Rat - Rat - Drama Script<br><br></span>The atmosphere in front of the school on an afternoon after school . <span>Seen a school kid named Derrick bought some peanuts from a bag shop .<br><br></span><span>He soon returned to rumahnya.Anting Pendan Swarovski Crystals 3D Dome AKS10<br><br></span>Deri home atmosphere . Deri opened his shoes and socks . He just put it in the back door of his house . He then immediately went to his room . <span>His mother saw action Deri .<br><br></span>Mother : ( angry ) \" Derrick , do not put your shoes carelessly . <span>Kan , already the mother provide special shelf for storing shoes . \"<br><br></span>Derrick : ( wiping sweat from his brow ) \" right Deri tired , Mom . Today its sultry taste really. <span>Anyway , right there Surti Bi . \"<br><br></span>Mother : \" Bi Surti returned home for three days . <span>Anyway , why do you ask Bi Surti ? \"<br><br></span><span>Deri \" Surti Bi Usually it is like clearing my shoes . \"<br><br></span><span>Mother : ( annoyed ) \" For something like this , you could sense Mrs. ngerjakannya own . \"<br><br></span><span>Derrick : ( immediately took his shoes and socks that had a jumble ) \" Aahh ... Mom . \"<br><br></span>Deri immediately went into his room . Atmosphere of the room changed to Deri . In the room , there is a small bed , a fan , a desk , and a trash can . Deri lay down on his bed . He threw his bag to the side under the desk. He had not changed his uniform . <span>Then , he turned on the fan.<br><br></span><span>Derrick : ( while reading a book that he takes from the desk study ) \" Ahh ... so it better .... \"<br><br></span>Deri unwrapping beans that he bought earlier. <span>He opened one by one and just throw peanut shells under his bed .<br><br></span>Atmosphere of the night . Derrick could not sleep . <span>He heard strange noises .<br><br></span>Ciiitttt ... cit ... cittt .... Deri fear . <span>From under his bed , out of a rat .<br><br></span>Deri shocked . He is most afraid of mice . Not long ago , few rats out from under his bed . <span>Derrick took the broom fibers .<br><br></span><span>Derrick : ( trying to repel the rats ) \" Ukhhh ... disturb it! \" ( Hit a rat )<br><br></span><span>Some rats even approached Deri .<br><br></span><span>Derrick : ( scared and screaming ) \" Mommy, Mommy tolongin Derrick ! \"<br><br></span><span>Mother : ( opening the room door Deri ) \"What you really shout ? \"<br><br></span><span>Derrick : ( pale face ) \" Mother , many si Jerry ! \"<br><br></span><span>Mother : \" Jerry , who &#039;s Jerry ? \"<br><br></span><span>Derrick : ( pointing under his bed ) \" mean Deri many small rodents . \"<br><br></span><span>Mother : ( confused ) \"Where ? \"<br><br></span><span>Derrick : \" It was under the bed Deri !<br><br></span>Deri fear . <span>Derrick does not want to sleep in the room Deri . \"<br><br></span><span>Mother : \"Well , tonight you&#039;re sleeping with your sister alone . \"<br><br></span>Atmosphere the morning . <span>Mom came into the room<br><br></span>Deri . <span>He was surprised to see garbage strewn under the bed Deri .<br><br></span><span>Mother : ( shouting , his face sullen )<br><br></span><span>\" Derii ... here ! \"<br><br></span><span>Derrick : ( wearing school uniform ) \" Yes what is it , Mom ? \"<br><br></span>Mother : \" Look ! \" ( Pointing to garbage strewn ) \" You slob all. <span>No wonder a lot of rats in your room . \"<br><br></span><span>Derrick : ( embarrassed and downcast ) \" Out of what , then? \"<br><br></span>Mother : \" Well anyway, even asked . From now on you have to maintain the cleanliness of your room . You do not throw litter again . <span>Kan , already the mother provide the trash in your room ( pointing to the trash ) .<br><br></span><span>What needs to be Mom made \u200b\u200bsignpost warning here ? \"<br></span>Derrick : \"I could have been . <span>Deri promise not to throw litter again .<br></span><span>Deri cured at the Jerry - Jerry naughty . \"<br></span>Mother : ( smiles ) \" Well, now you go to school . <span>After school , you must clean up your room . \"<br></span><span>Derrick : \" Well , Mom ! \"<br></span><span>Since then , Derrick always maintain the cleanliness of his room .</span></span><br>",
                    "attachments": []
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "slug": "terjemah-kan-ke-dalam-bahasa-indonesia-announcement-the-schoo-996",
            "question": "terjemah kan ke dalam bahasa indonesia : *announcement* the school drama club is going to organize the \"snow white\" casts audition . For those who are interested to join the audition , please come to our office on saturday , 17 september , at 2 p.m to register . The following are the requirements: (1).your latest photograph of postcard side(2). The registration form (get it in the office). The audition will be held on monday . 23 september, at 9 a.m. The list of the slected candidates will be announced in a week. We do appreciate your participation. Thank you the comittee p.s.: no change for the registration from *jangan pake google transtlet*",
            "attachments": [],
            "answers": [
                {
                    "answer": "\u00a0<strong>pengumuman</strong> <br>klub drama sekolah akan mengadakan audisi \"snow white\" . Bagi siapa saja\u00a0 yang tertarik untuk bergabung audisi, silahkan datang ke kantor kami pada hari Sabtu 17 September, pukul 2 siang untuk mendaftar. Berikut ini adalah persyaratan:.<br>\u00a0(1) foto terbaru Anda sisi kartu pos <br>(2). Formulir pendaftaran (mendapatkannya di kantor). <br>Audisi akan diadakan pada hari Senin. 23 September, pukul 9 pagi Daftar calon terpilih akan diumumkan dalam seminggu. Kami menghargai partisipasi Anda. Terima kasih p.s komite: tidak ada perubahan untuk pendaftaran .",
                    "attachments": []
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "slug": "apakah-artinya-lapangan-sepak-bola-dalam-bahasa-inggris-313",
            "question": "Apakah artinya lapangan sepak bola dalam bahasa inggris",
            "attachments": [],
            "answers": [
                {
                    "answer": "<span>football field</span> jawabanya<br>",
                    "attachments": []
                },
                {
                    "answer": "football field : lapangan sepak bola",
                    "attachments": []
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "slug": "the-pen-is-mightier-than-a-swordwhat-is-the-meaning-of-this-pr-831",
            "question": "The pen is mightier than a sword.What is the meaning of\u00a0 this proverb?\u00a0",
            "attachments": [],
            "answers": [
                {
                    "answer": "pen is mightier than a sword artinya kemampuan berkomunikasi (baik secara lisan maupun tulisan) jauh lebih efektif daripada kekerasan senjata.",
                    "attachments": []
                },
                {
                    "answer": "kata kata lebih tajam daripada sebuah pedang, maksudnya kata kata jika disalahgunakan bisa membuat orang terluka.",
                    "attachments": []
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "slug": "apa-arti-nya-i-like-this-461",
            "question": "Apa arti nya i like this",
            "attachments": [],
            "answers": [
                {
                    "answer": "\u00a0i like this artimya\u00a0aku suka ini \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0",
                    "attachments": []
                },
                {
                    "answer": "Saya suka ini :D<br>gampang sekali<br><br>",
                    "attachments": []
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "slug": "descripition-text-about-museum-fatahillah-3-paraghraphs-106",
            "question": "Descripition text about museum fatahillah (3 paraghraphs)",
            "attachments": [],
            "answers": [
                {
                    "answer": "The Jakarta history museum, also known as<em> Fatahillah Museum</em> or <em>Batavia Museum,</em> is located in the Old Town, Jakarta City, Indonesia. The building was built in 1710 as the <em>Stadhuis (city hal) </em>of batavia . It&#039;s opened in 1974. This building was the administrative headquarters of the <strong>Dutch East India Company and </strong>later of the<strong> Dutch Government. </strong>The current building was constructed in 1707 by the city government.<br><strong><br></strong>The building resembles the Dam place in Amsterdam, consist of a main building with two wings on the east and west\u00a0as well as sanding building used as offices, court rooms, and underground spaces are used as a prison. Facilities are library, diner museum, souvenir shop, cinema fatahilah, mosque, etc<br><strong><br></strong>Ativity. from 2001-2002 the jakarta history museum of arts program held every week nusantara II and IV for all 2003 jakarta history museum. This event focuses on the nuances of betawi art<strong><br><br><br><br></strong>",
                    "attachments": []
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "slug": "contoh-text-descriptive-tentang-benda-kesayangan-936",
            "question": "CONTOH TEXT DESCRIPTIVE TENTANG BENDA KESAYANGAN",
            "attachments": [],
            "answers": [
                {
                    "answer": "Boneka beruang pemberian ayahnya\u00a0adalah benda kesayangan Anya. Boneka beruang atau populer dengan nama \"Teddy bear\" adalah jenis boneka\u00a0untuk anak-anak dan orang dewasa. Namanya berasal dari Theodore Roosevelt, Presiden Amerika Serikatke-26, yang nama panggilannya adalah \"Teddy\" dan senang berburu beruang. Konon suatu hari di Hotel Colorado di Glenwood Springs, Colorado, Roosevelt kembali dari perburuan yang tidak berhasil dan pegawai hotel memberinya boneka beruang tersebut. Ketika Roosevelt memberikan boneka itu kepada anaknya, Alice, ia memberinya nama Teddy. Teddy bear memiliki bulu pendek yang lembut dan biasa berwarna cokelat dan warna-warna gradasi dari cokelat. Banyak aksesoris yang bisa dipakaikan di boneka Teddy seperti pakaian dan topi.\u00a0Boneka yang berukuran mulai dari sepuluh centimeter hingga dua meter ini umum diberikan sebagai ungkapan kasih sayang.",
                    "attachments": []
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "slug": "definisikegunaan-dan-pola-kalimat-dari-because-of-due-to-dan-th-432",
            "question": "Definisi,Kegunaan dan pola kalimat dari because of, due to dan thanks to .. tolong jawab dalam bahasa inggris ya",
            "attachments": [],
            "answers": [
                {
                    "answer": "because ; karena<br>itu buat memberikan penjelasan atau sebab [provide an explanation or reason for]",
                    "attachments": []
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "slug": "sebutkan-contoh-singular-dan-plural-dari-regular-dan-irregularse-473",
            "question": "Sebutkan contoh singular dan plural dari regular dan irregular,selengkap lengkapnya ?",
            "attachments": [],
            "answers": [
                {
                    "answer": "Singular and Plural Nouns\n\n<span>\n\n</span>\n\nKata benda atau nomina mempunyai dua bentuk (form) kata, yaitu singular dan plural.<br>\nSingular nouns digunakan untuk menunjukkan suatu benda yang berjumlah tunggal atau satu, misalnya:  a computer, a chair, a train, a player, a teacher, a taxi, etc. Sedangkan plural nouns digunakan untuk menunjukkan benda yang berjumlah banyak (jamak), misalnya: computers, chairs, trains, players, teachers, taxis, etc.<br><br>Singular nouns umumnya disertai determiners (a/an, this, that, the), misalnya: a river, a castle, an idea, this book, the man, etc.<br><br>\nUmumnya plural nouns dibentuk dengan menambah huruf -s di belakang kata benda yang akan dibuat dalam bentuk jamak, misalnya: boats, bats, houses, rivers, computer, boys, girls, etc.<br><br>\nPerhatikan catatan dan contoh pembentukan plural nouns berikut di bawah ini.<br><br>\nNomina yang berakhiran -s, -ss, -ch, -sh atau \u2013x ditambah akhiran \u2013es. <br>\n- bus  --&gt; buses<br>\n- glass --&gt; glasses<br>\n- dress  --&gt; dresses<br>\n- branch --&gt; branches<br>\n- church --&gt; churches<br>\n- beach --&gt; beaches<br>\n- sandwich --&gt; sandwiches<br>\n- witch --&gt; witches<br>\n- brush  --&gt; brushes<br>\n- flash --&gt; flashes<br>\n- box  --&gt; boxes<br>\n- fox --&gt; foxes<br><br>\nNomina yang berakhiran \u2013y, diganti dengan i kemudian ditambah \u2013es.<br>\n- baby --&gt; babies<br>\n- family --&gt; families<br>\n- story --&gt; stories<br>\n- fairy --&gt; fairies<br>\n- puppy --&gt; puppies<br>\n- housefly --&gt; houseflies<br>\n- library --&gt; libraries<br>\n- city --&gt; cities<br>\n- lily --&gt; lilies<br>\n- party --&gt; parties<br>\n- dictionary --&gt; dictionaries<br><br>\nNomina berakhiran \u2013y yang sebelumnya terdapat huruf hidup atau vokal (vowel), langsung ditambah akhiran \u2013s. Kecuali nomina yang berakhiran \u2013quy, -y diganti dengan i kemudian ditambah \u2013es (soliloquy --&gt; soliloquies).<br>\n- key --&gt; keys<br>\n- monkey --&gt; monkeys<br>\n- donkey --&gt; donkeys<br>\n- toy --&gt; toys<br>\n- boy --&gt; boys<br>\n- cowboy --&gt; cowboys<br>\n- day --&gt; days<br>\n- tray --&gt; trays<br>\n- runway --&gt; runways<br>\n- chimney --&gt; chimneys<br>\n- trolley --&gt; trolleys<br>\n- valley --&gt; valleys<br><br>\nNomina yang berakhiran \u2013f, diganti dengan v kemudian ditambah \u2013es.<br>\n- half --&gt; halves<br>\n- leaf --&gt; leaves<br>\n- shelf --&gt; shelves<br>\n- wolf --&gt; wolves<br>\n- thief --&gt; thieves<br><br>\nBeberapa nomina yang berakhiran \u2013f, hanya ditambah akhiran \u2013s.<br>\n- chief --&gt; chiefs<br>\n- roof --&gt; roofs<br>\n- handkerchief --&gt; handkerchiefs<br>\n- cliff --&gt; cliffs<br>\n- puff --&gt; puffs<br><br>\nDan beberapa nomina yang berakhiran \u2013f bisa dijadikan plural dengan dua cara di atas.<br>\n- scarf --&gt; scarfs or scarves<br>\n- hoof --&gt; hoofs or hooves<br>\n- dwarf --&gt; dwarfs or dwarves<br>\n- wharf --&gt; wharfs or wharves<br><br><span></span><br>",
                    "attachments": []
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "slug": "yang-benar-we-did-an-opening-ceremony-atau-we-did-the-opening-cer-713",
            "question": "Yang benar we did an opening ceremony atau we did the opening ceremony?",
            "attachments": [],
            "answers": [
                {
                    "answer": "we did the opening ceremony\u00a0<br><br>",
                    "attachments": []
                },
                {
                    "answer": "we did the opening ceremony..",
                    "attachments": []
                }
            ]
        }
    ]
}